search-safely.com 2018-03-15

# WebDiscover Browser

Thank you for visiting GetWebDiscover.com (the "Site"). The Site is an Internet property of WebDiscover Media, and its affiliated companies ("WebDiscover Media", “our”, "we" or "us"). This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") outlines the privacy practices and policies associated with the Site and in relation to any information that you may share with us when you access and use the Site, and through your use of the WebDiscover Browser (the “Browser”).

* * *

#### 1\. Personal Information

When you purchase, download trial or evaluation versions, or register for any software products and/or services made available through the Site, and/or Browser, we may collect personal information that you submit including without limitation your name, address, electronic mail (email) address, phone number, and credit card information (collectively, your “Personal Information”) for the purposes of recording the transaction when you engage in activities on the Site, through use of the Browser, or within any software products or services provided by us. If and when we use a third party payment processing merchant, we ensure that the same privacy criteria as defined herein are in place with such merchant. We do not (knowingly) collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen. We also give users the option of receiving useful product information (such as Browser updates, software product or service updates, and associated product and service offerings), via email. We fully ensure your privacy and value your trust. We will never sell, rent, lease or trade your personal information to any third party. Likewise, your information will not be shared with a third party in any other way unless we are required to do so in order to complete a transaction initiated by you or as required to be disclosed by law or to an applicable regulatory or governing body. WebDiscover Media may engage the services of a third party from time to time and may be required to provide certain information that includes your personal information in order for the third party to perform such services. Any third parties who provide services to WebDiscover Media have agreed not to disclose your information or use it for any other purpose, and are required to implement or adopt a Privacy Policy that is no less stringent than this Privacy Policy. If you are receiving email communications from WebDiscover Media, you may opt-out of receiving emails from us at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email or by visiting our website at www.getwebdiscover.com. By choosing to enter and submit the requested information when prompted, you are consenting to our collection, use, and disclosure of such information for the purposes as outlined herein.

#### 2\. Anonymous Information

“Anonymous Information” is information other than Personal Information, which may include the domain names, IP addresses and type of browsers that you may use, URLs you have visited, referring URLs, and other, non-personally identifiable information.

When you access any site or service covered by this Privacy Policy, we collect Anonymous Information. We use this information for system administration, for market research (which may be shared with third parties), to personalize your experience on our site, with the Browser, to show you more relevant advertising messages based on the URLs you have visited, and, generally, to improve our products and/or services. We share this Anonymous Information with selected third parties and business partners in order to deliver to you more relevant advertising messages.

WebDiscover Media will not share any Anonymous Information if that information is or will be linked to your Personal Information, unless we have given you notice as described above and you have given us authorization to do so.

WebDiscover Media can and will use IP addresses to identify users of our site when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site's policies, or to protect our products, services, Site, the Browser, or other users.

#### 3\. Sharing Personal Information

We will not share your Personal Information unless we have first given you notice that we might share your data, and you have authorized us to do so. Our business partners who receive information from us have the right to use the data we provide them (sometimes, in connection with other information they may have gathered about you), but are generally prohibited from sharing this information with other companies or people.

In certain special cases, we may disclose your Personal Information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or otherwise injuring or interfering with WebDiscover Media' rights, property or operations, other WebDiscover Media users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your Personal Information when we believe the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case or administrative investigation.

Finally, where, in our sole discretion after undertaking such investigation or investigations as we see fit, we determine that you have engaged in conduct which might be considered, unlawful, fraudulent, or which might harm or damage the reputation or standing of WebDiscover Media with either the general public or with a business partner or potential business partner of WebDiscover Media, we reserve the right to release your Personal Information to such persons or third parties as we consider necessary in order to prevent you from causing injury to, or otherwise injuring or interfering, now or in the future, with WebDiscover Media' rights, property or operations or otherwise the rights, property or operations of anyone else who could be harmed by such conduct.

#### 4\. Third Party Relationships

**Third Party Links -** The Site, Browser, software products, and services may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites and, where you request information from third party providers, WebDiscover Media may transfer you directly to the websites of such third party providers. WebDiscover Media is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be required to provide certain information to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and WebDiscover Media has no responsibility or liability relating to them. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of such website. These third party entities are independent third parties and are not affiliated with WebDiscover Media.

**Third Party Offers -** WebDiscover Media may provide its users with the opportunity to receive special offers, products and/or services from third parties. Where you indicate the desire to receive certain offers, products or services from a third party during the applicable information collection process, your personally identifiable information that was provided during that information collection process will be shared with the applicable third party so that such third party may provide their products and/or services to you so that you do not have to complete another information collection form to purchase or receive that product or service.

**Third Party Cookies -** Clicking on any third party offers may add and place cookies from third party affiliate marketers on to your computer prior to directing you to the applicable advertiser’s site. Cookies from third party affiliate marketers are used only for tracking and reporting purposes. No personally identifiable information is collected or stored by the Browser during this process.

**Third Party Technology and Services -** The web search services available on the Site, through the Browser, or made available through any of our software products and/or services, as applicable, are provided by SafestSearch Search and powered by SafestSearch search partners and/or any third party search partners contracted by WebDiscover Media. For information on the SafestSearch Search web search services data collection, please visit <http://info.safestsearches.com/privacy-policy/>, or visit the applicable search provider's privacy policy. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies of such third party technology and service providers. The third party entities that are providing the web search services are independent third parties and are not affiliated with WebDiscover Media. 

#### 5\. Opt-out Unsubscribe

When you submit your information through the Site, you have opted-in to receive information and future communications from us. To opt-out of having future email communications from us, please contact [privacy@getwebdiscover.com](mailto:privacy@getwebdiscover.com) or follow the opt-out request process in the applicable email communication. When you submit personally identifiable information through the Site, and/or Browser, to receive information and marketing communications from any third party providers, you may be contacted by these third party providers. If you do not wish to receive future communications from the third party providers, you should notify them directly of your choices regarding the use of your information. To opt-out of having future third party marketing communications sent to you, you will be required to unsubscribe with the applicable third party providers.

#### 6\. Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### 7\. Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you. Notice regarding any Privacy Policy changes will be placed in a prominent location on the Site and will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

#### 8\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us:

WebDiscover Media  
#185 – 911 Yates St.  
Suite 327  
Victoria, BC V8V 4Y9  
Canada  
1 (250) 590-1097
